https://www.desertrat.com/p-33172-privacy-policy.html

Privacy Policy
Our Commitment To Privacy
Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.
The Information We Collect:
This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the Desertrat.com website. On some pages, you can order products, make requests, and register to receive materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages are Name, Address, Email address, Phone number, and Credit/Debit Card Information.
On some pages, you can submit information about other people. For example, if you order a gift online and want it sent directly to the recipient, you will need to submit the recipient's address. In this circumstance, the types of personal information collected are: Name, Address, Phone Number, Email address.
The Way We Use Information:
We use the information you provide about yourself when placing an order only to complete that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order. We use the information you provide about someone else when placing an order only to ship the product and to confirm delivery. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order.
We offer gift-cards by which you can personalize a product you order for another person. Information you provide to us to create a gift-card is only used for that purpose, and it is only disclosed to the person receiving the gift.
We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties.
You can register with our website if you would like to receive updates on our new products and services. Information you submit on our website will not be used for this purpose unless you fill out the registration form.
We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website. For example, we may notice that X number of individuals visited a certain area on our website, or that Y number of men and Z number of women filled out our registration form, but we would not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals. Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.
Our Commitment To Data Security
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
Our system is secured by a Cisco PIX Firewall and data is encrypted up to 256-bits for safe purchasing.
How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information
You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by logging in with your user and password. We use this procedure to better safeguard your information. You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error. To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.
For questions regarding our privacy policy please contact us at .
Shop Now
Tires
Shop Tires Shop All »
Shop Tire & Wheel Packages Shop All »
Shop Wheels Shop All »
Shop UTV/ATV Tires Shop All »
Shop UTV/ATV Wheels Shop All »
Shop Lighting Shop All »
Shop Towing & Load Control Shop All »
Shop Drivetrain & Differential Shop All »
Shop Electrical Shop All »
Shop Engine Performance Shop All »
Shop Exterior Shop All »
Shop Interior Shop All »
Shop Jeep Products & Accessories Shop All »
Shop Overland Camping Shop All »
Shop Storage Shop All »
Shop Suspension Products Shop All »
Shop Tools Shop All »
Shop Towing & Air Systems Shop All »
Shop Wheel Accessories Shop All »
Shop Winch & Recovery Shop All »
Shop Books & DVD Shop All »
Off Road DVD
Trail Books & Maps
Logo & Wearables
Shop Logo & Wearables Shop All »
Forgot Password »
